Viewers all over the world, I know you are feeling his presence.
Where can we go from his presence?
Give thanks to God
The SCOAN Sunday Service
We have many people here today that are waiting for healing.
As we were dancing, singing - they were unable because of the pain and affliction.
I think the best way to celebrate this Palm Sunday [April 9, 2017] is to bless them with healing and deliverance.
So that the coming one, they can be happy to celebrate it.
That is the purpose of Palm Sunday.
Really.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Make sure people are happy, just as you are.
Are you happy?
I can't hear you.
Tell your neighbour: I want to make sure you are happy as I am!
[I want to make sure you are happy as I am!]
Tell your neighbour.
Tell the viewers all over the world.
[I want to make sure you are happy as I am]
Tell the viewers all over the world - they are there.
[I want to make sure you are happy as I am!]
Those on the sickbed.
Many are on the sickbed, and they are watching you.
Can you please tell them:
You want to make sure that they are happy as you are.
[I want to make sure you are happy as I am!]
Many are in the prison yard. Tell them
Those watching the programme, tell them.
[I want to make sure you are happy as I am!]
The SCOAN Sunday Service
You can only give that happiness when you have it.
That is why Christians have to be happy.
When you are not happy, you cannot give.
It is what you have that you can give out of.
You cannot give all - you can only give out of what you have.
When you are not happy, you cannot.
Even when you give money - when you are not happy and you now give money to your neighbour,
it is like you are giving sorrow.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
When you are not happy and you are rich
and your neighbor runs to you for help and you are not happy,
whatever you give out of that unhappiness is sorrow.
Your neighbour cannot use it for anything.
Therefore, what you've been giving in the past - think about it.
The mood you were in when you were giving those things.
Whatever you give that is not joyful is not from God.
Happiness can only come from God.
Whatever that is out of unhappiness is not from God.
If you pretend to smile and you are not happy - that is not from God.
This is why many things you are giving out - there is no reward from God -
because you are not giving it out of happiness.
You are giving something and after giving it, you are now saying to yourself,
"Oh! Had I known, I would not have given this.
Oh, my God. Well, I have to give it because they will do this or that to me".
It means you are not giving it out of God.
You cannot expect a reward from God and God is the rewarder.
Or you greet a brother of yours, "Good morning, sir!"
He says, "Oh, thank you!" After your brother turns his back, you do this...
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Can you see why you have not been receiving rewards.
You are a good giver but no rewards.
Or in the past, you trained many people to university, to college, you assisted many.
In those days, many of your younger ones lived with you.
You trained them. Now some of them have become great.
If you remember when you were training them, you gave out of unhappiness.
Some of them when you gave them money, you threw it - "I have to give you, stupid boy!"
"Foolish boy!" You just had to give them.
Today they are becoming great - but something is telling them that they should just leave you the way you are.
If you had given all those things out of God...
God is the rewarder.
You have not been helping out of God.
You help but not out of God.
You give but not out of God.
You give out of complaining.
You greet out of complaining, grumbling.
You smile out of grumbling.
It is better not to give than to give out of grumbling.
You help someone with millions of dollars out of grumbling.
You cannot expect a reward from God.
Your grumbling is not of God.
The act that follows that help will determine the kind of help you give.
I want to help you. How are you?
Let me help you!
It is not that help that matters but the force that follows that help.
It's not that help I'm doing but the force behind it will determine the kind of reward I will receive.
But people seeing us will say, "Oh, this man is very kind. He helped this man to stand up.
Look at him - very humble".
"Let's go." The man cannot walk. "Oh, very humble."
What is wrong with you?
Thank you. The man cannot walk.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
This man - eh! Everything - "Holy Spirit, Holy Spirit!"
You see me. Maybe I am just wearing a simple dress.
You are not expecting me to wear this and you say, "The man is humble".
Who told you I am humble because I wear a rag?
I can be very proud and at the same time wear a simple thing.
It is not what you see but the force behind what you see.
Tell your neighbour.
[It is not what you see but the force behind what you see.]
I can't hear you.
This is why the Bible says: We don't walk by sight; we walk by faith.
What I am seeing now - "A very humble, gentle man."
"Look at the simple dress."
Do you know the force behind what he is doing?
Look at money.
If you put blood money down and clean money, would you be able to know the difference?
When there is no blood on the money?
Maybe someone just went out to rob, killed the person and carried millions of dollars
and now wants to use this as charity.
But it is money you will see -
you don't know where he brought the money from, and the money is clean as well as the godly one.
If you now see them side by side, you won't know the difference.
It is the force behind the money that determines the type of money it is.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
The force behind a man determines the type of man he is.
"A very humble man, what a godly man" - and yet he is not godly.
"He is a leader, he likes God - a humble and very good man."
Who told you he is good, who told you he is humble?
It is the force, and this force - we cannot see it with our eyes.
It is the force that determines the reward.
This is why sometimes you say, "This man is trying to work hard; why is he suffering?"
Who told you he is trying, he works hard
when we are not judged by what we see but what we cannot see.
As a believer, you are not judged by going to church, by reading the Bible.
This is why we say "spirit of humility", "spirit of goodness".
If those spirits are removed, anybody can demonstrate whatever you call it.
You can pretend to be humble.
The spirit behind it would determine whether you are pretending or not.
People like me, I'm scared when it is time for thanksgiving
because I don't know where you are coming from - with your money.
Many can come with blood money.
When it is time for offering, they would raise their offering whereas it is blood money.
What can the man of God use that kind of blood money for?
Is he going to bless the man?
This is why we, ministers of God, have so much to do.
Tell your neighbour: What we received from our members as offering at thanksgiving is killing us.
[What we received from our members as offering at thanksgiving is killing us.]
The SCOAN Sunday Service
When you see money carried in the church - offering money - the bowl is full of money,
inside that - there is good and killer inside.
Wicked people like the pastor to ask.
When the pastor does not ask, they cannot give.
When the pastor does not ask and recognise them, they cannot give.
They like praise, they like recognition.
If you want to do away and avoid these people, these people will not put money inside.
Don't praise them! Let them know it is to God they give and not to you.
Don't even receive it directly!
If you don't receive something directly from the killer,
the killer will not give you because he wants to be recognised.
They like praise - that is their reward - because they have no reward from God.
Their reward is that praise to know them and to recognise them; it is their reward.
What comes from God goes to God.
If what you have is from God, it will go to God.
You don't need any recognition from the pastor - whatever you want to give to God, you give.
Look at me, I'm moving.
It's not this movement that matters but the force behind this movement
determines whether I am moving of God or I am moving of satan.
Now I want to pray for this man. I am walking towards him.
This movement does not matter but the force - who is leading you,
what force is behind this move - it will determine the reward!
The SCOAN Sunday Service
No one can get healed without faith.
If I am coming and I have doubt in my heart - "Will this man be healed?" - and that doubt fills my heart,
if I pray for this man, I will ask him to come back tomorrow.
That is the method of doubt - "Come back again tomorrow and let us see your condition."
When faith is now, faith acts now, believes now, confesses now.
Faith acts now.
Tell your neighbour.
[Faith acts now.]
Faith heals now.
Faith delivers now.
Faith blesses now.
That is faith!
Faith is present tense.
And if you're not of God - there's no neutral place - if you are not of God, you are of satan.
If you are of God, then you will be filled with faith
because only faith moves, talks and walks with Him.
If you are not of God, you will be filled with doubt.
I want to pray with you.
Doubt: "Will this prayer be answered? Would God answer me?" Because I am not of Him.
If I now pray, it's not going to happen.
The only excuse I will give you is to come back.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Don't let us deceive ourselves.
90% of your action cannot be judged on the outside
but the force behind your action determines where your action comes from.
Everybody says, "In the name of Jesus!"
They cannot just because of that say that they are calling Jesus.
You can be calling Jesus but the force behind that calling is of satan.
You don't need a licence to call the name Jesus.
But whenever you call Him genuinely, you need a licence from Jesus.
When you call Jesus genuinely, you need what? - Licence.
A licence means you will be adopted by the Holy Spirit to call that name genuinely.
In the same vein, you are free to have a copy of the Bible.
All you need is money. If you have that money, just walk into the bookshop.
They will not ask you whether you are a Christian or whatever.
They need money to give you a copy of the Bible.
When we know this, we will be able to train our children, ourselves and our friends.
Don't let anybody deceive you with their appearance
or when they say, "Good morning, sir!"
After that "good morning, sir", you can turn your back and they will be the ones to kill you.
Or somebody responsible for a death - while people are crying, he, the killer, will now come back.
He will rush there and start crying.
He would be the one to cry and jump around and people will say, "Don't die, it's alright!"
whereas he is the one that killed the deceased.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Is that not action?
He would cry genuinely, tears would come out - not that he pretends - you see tears coming out.
He would be the one joining them, shouting, crying, "He is my brother, my dear friend"
- and he would be cursing the person who killed the man:
"God will do this, God will do that!", and he is the one that...
What do we do about this?
The SCOAN Sunday Service
In the service, you can call the name Jesus a million times -
just as a demonstration to show people that you are a believer, a true man of God.
So, please...
It is the force behind accomplishment.
The force behind what? - Accomplishment.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
God loves you. Thank you.
Viewers, thank you.
The SCOAN Sunday Service